And we are live. Let's go.
>> Yes, hello, hello.
>> Hi Mitchell. How are you doing?
>> Oh, it was delayed. I was still waiting
on a YouTube, but now it's now it's
counting down. Perfect.
>> Oh, okay. So, but it works. We are live.
We are live live. People enjoy it. And
comment and subscribe.
So,
>> Everything.
>> How's your week?
>> Uh busy.
>> Yeah?
>> Again.
>> Yeah.
>> Testing, building, watching for the new
versions, waiting on Fable, but we got
surprised.
>> Yes. I mean, it was like 4 months ago
that they released like Sony 4.6. So,
yeah, I would think.
>> Yeah.
>> Possible thing.
>> We got a new one.
And it's better, right?
>> Oh, yeah. The Yeah, Sony Sony 5. Yeah,
so
yeah, we're going to talk about that,
but like
yeah, I like it. I I like Sony and even
like uh
it changed the workflow. And even this
week with like the all of the automation
and stuff that I set up, don't I I run
the task on
uh Codex
>> Mhm.
>> and GPT 5.5 and stuff. And excite
because they always reset it. So, I'm
just like boom boom boom. And I have to
use the limit credits, too.
>> It [snorts] feels like we got like six
accounts this month.
>> Yeah, exactly. And
um so, I I I build with 5.5 XI
>> Mhm.
>> and I review with Opus 4.8 Ultra code,
whatever. So, all of the PR are getting
reviewed by Opus.
>> Mhm.
That's awesome. Yeah. So, what are we
going to talk about today?
>> Okay, yeah, yeah, okay, okay, okay. Bro,
like you are invited.
>> We can do the intro. Yes.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Okay, so let's do the intro and then I
can
for the video is going to be good. Okay,
cool.
Um
Okay.
Fiber 5 is back. Woo. Wait, wait.
>> Fireworks.
>> That was loud. Fireworks,
fireworks, what do we do fireworks?
I forgot.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh puff puff puff puff. Yes. Oh, that's
loud as [__]
Oh, yeah, okay. So,
>> [laughter]
>> Fiber 5 is back and we also got a little
surprise from the little brothers Sony
5. And
if you read the timeline it said that a
good model or it said that like
expensive. So, we're going to discuss
about that because yeah, I'm I'm not
sure personally. Have you checked the
prices?
>> Uh no. I use everything within a
subscription and I didn't update my APIs
yet.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So, yeah.
Is that really the model that everyone
was expecting? Probably not, but we got
it. We're going to use it. And
tomorrow like Fiber 5 will come back
soon enough so we can burn even more
token.
But
how is that going to match on our on our
workflow automation and workflow that we
have set up? We are going to see that in
that video. So, subscribe, like the
video, comments, and thank you.
Woo. Right. Okay.
Nice.
Uh okay. So, Fiber 5.
>> Yeah. Do you think that when Fiber comes
back it's directly just API only?
>> So,
yeah, they talked about that in the
announcement, too.
But for Fiber 5 it will No, no, it's
subscription, but they're going to stop
it. They're going to give us a few days
to test it on a subscription and it's
going to be only 50% of the subscription
max that way you can use Fable.
>> Yeah. So, it's a bit like drugs again.
Here is a little bit, use it.
>> Exactly. There is so many children again
for Fable 5. It's nuts.
>> Yeah.
>> But okay, so first
the little brother Sony 5.
Okay, so same design, same logo. Okay,
that's cool.
Which is Okay, that I like.
The benchmark again for Sony 5
against 4.8.
That's cool because it's almost the same
thing and
from 4.6 to 5 we got from Agile coding
like the terminal bench 2.1 from 67 to
80%.
>> That's a lot.
>> That's insane. And yeah, the other
benchmark Okay, it's a lot. Whatever
computer use cool and knowledge work.
Yeah, knowledge work it's even above
4.8.
>> Yeah, but just a little little bit.
>> Yeah.
>> Nothing too big, but
>> But the pricing
cloud
pricing
tag
path
Let's go.
Okay. Nope, not this one.
>> Nope.
Different pricing.
>> pricing API
tag
Okay, yeah, let's go.
Tag tag I'm going to do.
but
Okay.
Tag tag. So,
4.8 is 5 in
and
>> 25 out
and Sony 5 okay, so until August 31st,
two in and 10 out.
For the same benchmark.
>> Yeah.
That's that's a lot cheaper.
>> And after that it's going to do
>> 15
>> 50% on top.
>> Yeah.
So
>> By September 1st, we will have like
Sonet 7 if it's going in this base.
>> Yeah, could be too.
>> [laughter]
>> But
yeah, like
It's from now that's that's great. And I
mean okay, so that's the price of the
the model itself, but
>> What is the difference in price with the
previous Sonet?
>> Uh
>> So the 4.6.
>> Yes.
>> How much more expensive did they make
it?
>> 4.6
So three in and 15 out. What?
>> Yeah, that's the that's the same price
for five. So you can just update your
API to five and pay nothing additional.
>> Yeah, it's even Yeah, okay.
>> Because of the discount they give you.
>> Yes.
>> So if you have an API, update it.
Put it on five.
>> We do that. But also
That's the pricing per token, but it
depends of the how many token the model
is using to do a task.
>> Yes.
>> So
yeah, because A cool is like one in and
five out, but I know I never use A cool.
Like it for with open clue A cool was
just to do the heartbeat.
>> Well, I tried it and it gave me
such bad results that I skipped it after
30 minutes of testing.
>> I know exactly. Like nobody's using A
cool whatsoever, right? Uh
But again, like yeah, if you have a big
task with Sony.
And
um
it take less token to use than it can be
even cheaper than some open source model
that are way cheaper per token, but it
take 45 minutes to do a task that it
will take 5 minutes to do Sony and burn
like 10 times more tokens. So,
yeah, those those benchmark are tricky
and it needs to be output based. But,
how do you measure the input anyway?
>> Well, you have to do the exact same
prompt for each model, right?
>> Um
>> So, you make like a small easy prompt
and then you go bigger like you have 10
and you try all 10 of them and see how
many tokens they use.
>> Yeah, but the problem with that is like
once we have a
the the the test where the model can be
trained on, then it will perform way
better on that
>> Yeah.
>> test and then it's fixed. So, yeah, it's
>> But, that's in every test.
>> Yeah, I know exactly.
>> for that one.
>> Yeah, exactly. And so, that that's
really tricky based on
uh yeah, like those those benchmark are
tricky. That's why we need to test it
for your own code base and like
implementation. And even from one code
base to an another, like for example
from a yeah, JavaScript mono repo to a
PHP project, I don't know how the AI
uh
are reacting to it differently. Because
historically, maybe there is more PHP
code and also maybe not.
>> Yeah, well, it depends a lot. It also
depends do you have a framework that he
knows or do you have something
completely custom built? Do you have
documentation in it?
Adding um explanation in your files
helps a lot.
>> Yeah.
>> Because I've noticed that if you put
explanation in your files above your
function, it reads it first and if it
understands that it doesn't need the
function, it doesn't read it. It just
skips it.
>> Mhm.
>> So, that saves some time and and tokens.
>> Oh, so you have an inline document like
you a GS Docs or PHP Docs stuff now?
>> And just say, "This This function is
used for new clients, and this function
is used for existing clients." So, then
it knows what function to use.
>> Also, code is low for real.
Uh And you don't have the same
documentation inside the MD files?
>> Yeah, I do.
>> Okay.
>> But, then it doesn't always I don't
know. It doesn't always read your MD
files.
>> Yeah. No. No. Like I I have an issue
with Okay, so Codex I'm fighting against
the Once the session is done, open a
pull request, commit, push, and pull
request. And Claude is
uh
today wiped out my work trees.
I say, "Oh, yeah, clean those work trees
in that project." And it clean it went
to clean the other project too. And it
said,
>> Yeah.
>> "Bro, what the fuck?"
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah. I had some spare time and spare
tokens, so I did everything.
>> Yeah, exactly.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh yeah. So, yeah, it's still tricky.
But, uh like we're getting really really
powerful models like uh
Do you ever look at the code anymore
still?
>> I do at the end. I check it.
>> Okay.
>> But, I still do even I don't only use
Opus for uh reviewing. I still have
Codex 5.5 finding issues that Codex of
uh that Opus doesn't find.
>> Okay. Yeah, I mean like both
models are good working together. Like
again, so
this week I've uh so I I kept set up
those automation in Codex and the Claude
desktop app.
So, now I have um
implementation like features
implementation taking from GitHub every
2 hours and I have a
pull request review every 6 hours and
then it merge to master and I'm I'm
about to put a auto deploy
to production
later this week maybe.
And because yeah, like okay, green up so
it's different. But so there is that and
um I also have like a routine of
refactoring and dry the code because
we have a lot of slope in the app so
those three those routine are required.
But
yeah, it's good and I didn't burn my
cloud subscription in 2 days this time.
So that's a win.
>> Yeah, I'm doing my best but I'm only
able to burn it fully.
>> Yeah.
Run automations.
>> Yeah. I'm still looking for I've been
seeing on the timeline some posts about
Grok.
>> Oh yeah.
>> How they are training it right now using
Grok to train it and installing and and
I know
yeah, all these companies.
>> Yeah.
>> So I'm really looking forward
to see the next model because I didn't
test it yet.
>> I mean 1.5 trillion parameters that's
going to be fun.
And uh there is a play maybe for Elon
Musk to launch Grok as a or even like
another model like he he can just redo
something else but open source.
>> Yeah, but he has so many things that he
can
have the AI learn like every car is
giving data, every Grok user is giving
data. I think Cloud and OpenAI are
behind on the amount of data that they
are inputting.
>> And and he has the compute and energy to
power a big gigantic model stuff.
>> He is already given Cloud some of his
resources, so
>> So, yeah.
>> I do think he has some spare left then,
right?
>> Mhm.
And and again, like if it's an open
source model, that that would be fun.
>> Yeah.
>> Because that yeah, we're going to talk
about like I think next week if we don't
have a 5.6 by then, we should definitely
do the open source model
uh uh live stream video and
um
like GL
GLM 5.2, it's really good, but
>> [laughter]
>> if you want to run it at home, you need
a half a million hardware to run that.
>> Yeah. Well, 5K should be enough, but
still.
>> Yeah, so
>> And then, I think even when you set it
up
when you when you buy the hardware, you
still need some IT knowledge to set it
up.
>> No, exactly. But I
No, it's it's not like those open source
model are getting getting like crazy.
So, then
that means you need to pay API keys, API
pricing for those models.
But then that means you also depends of
like
AWS Bedrock and whatever to run them on
open router. That means if
the US wants to
forbid you to use an open models from
China, then
>> it just blocks them.
>> Exactly.
>> Yeah, like they did now with Fable 5.
>> Yes.
So, that's fun. Like
>> So, I still think at home having your
own almost data center in the corner of
your room with like three fans blowing
at it so it doesn't overheat, it's a
good solution, but it's not as easy as
download, install, and ready to go.
>> Yeah, and what are you going to run on
it?
>> Uh
I have been researching people sell You
see a a of posts, people selling their
computer online.
>> Mhm.
>> Oh, really?
>> And then earning money by having other
people use their RAM and their
resources. But also that that's not
working as they tell you in the post.
>> No way. What What What a surprise. You
[laughter] read your next article and
half of it is [__]
>> Yeah, yeah, yeah, for sure. You see the
Have you seen the videos where they have
like
where they are saying we had a full data
center of Bitcoin miners and we
converted everything to AI token usage
so that people can rent out and now we
are doing a 5x compared to Bitcoin
mining. Well, I researched it and I
don't know how they do the math, but
they didn't use AI for it because it's
wrong.
>> Oh, yeah.
>> It's like the
Yeah, the most optimal
idea that you can have like 100% of the
time having a good price, not people on
the cutting you and everything.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, that's when you make the money,
not in real life.
>> Yeah, yeah, something like for Bitcoin
miners, right? Like you need to have a
electricity deal with like
your national provider to be worth it.
>> Yeah, it's it's not possible for a
normal person with his with his standard
house.
>> 100%. And look
what I found
on the timeline from Theo
versus Alex Finn.
They were talking about Sonic. It
happened. Cloud Sonic 5 released
dominated over 4.6 almost
a fraction of the price. Theo tweet, a
fraction of the price? I guess 1/3 of
1/2 is the definition of fraction.
>> [laughter]
>> It is the other way around.
>> Yeah, so that's exactly that kind of
content that make people read, but yeah.
>> Yeah, people read it, people don't
think, and then they go and use it.
>> Yeah.
>> And they will never post online that
they were the ones overpaying because of
>> I mean, that that's quite uh that
happened with Alex when uh he talked
about open models uh on his live stream
and stuff.
He
um he create content about them and it's
good it brings people in and stuff. But
then like
you you check the next live stream and
say, "Oh, yeah, by the way, my brain is
closed." Okay, cool. Cool, bro.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah, so and then you you buy hardware
of like, yeah, he he spend like uh 50
grand on DGX and like two Mac Mini to
like
um
use
models that have been like 6 months old,
but you can't do [__] with that. It's
not even like Sonnet 3.5
of intelligence.
>> And for running it locally, that's not
enough. You need to have external APIs
that are now burning a lot of tokens,
connect them to your locally set up. But
then you have to set up additional
VPN tunnels or whatever to make it
secure.
And nobody can do that like two clicks.
>> Exactly. And that's what Okay,
we are definitely doing the next week
live stream. But uh
Amazon Bedrock.
Like you need a EC2 instance
Bedrock to run any models and to be a
bit like uh
open source  uh you own the
models and you own the setup. But you're
still going to pay a few grand amounts
to
>> Yeah.
>> for that kind of intelligence. And if
you put few grand amounts on Bedrock,
then maybe it's better to pay a few
subscription on Cloud.
>> Yeah, of course.
>> Yeah. So
yeah, like the next few months, like the
next 12 to 18 months will be insane.
Like it's it's going to be fun.
>> Yeah.
>> But okay, should we go back to
>> This Sonnet 5.
>> Yes.
>> Uh [snorts] puff puff puff. So yeah,
benchmark good. We we like big numbers,
that's fine. Uh working with Cloud
Sonnet. Okay, so here cost per task. Um
Opus 4.8, Sonnet five. This this schema
is like this chart is bit weird because
it shows that Sonnet is more expensive
and a little bit more efficient but it's
almost the same [__]
>> Yeah. Well,
indeed, it's weird.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
But
um
with Fable five, like if we can compare
to Sonnet five, Opus 4.8 and Fable, that
should be
a more interesting chart, I think.
>> Mhm.
>> Okay, also also also, let me come back
to that. Okay. So, with Sonnet five,
it's
uh
Sonnet is used if you run Ultra code for
with Opus 4.8 and Fable, but Ultra code
with 4.8 use Sonnet is the sub agent
that Ultra code is calling.
>> Also the 5.0.
>> 5.0 like uh
>> Yeah, they're the version five.
>> Yes, yes. I I hope I think it does
because uh Sonnet is the default model
now. Like uh Sonnet five. So, you burn
on tokens for 4.8 and then you burn
token for Sonnet five, which is like
okay, not the same price as 4.6, we just
saw it. But
uh yeah, that's
then if it if it's not efficient enough
and it burn more token than 4.6, then
Ultra code 4.8 is going to be expensive
as [__]
>> Yeah, well, it feels like it's draining
your money because as soon as you set it
up and you see oh I'm deploying six
agents, then it's deploying 12, then it
goes to 48, and before you know you're
over 200 agents.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah, each one taking your money saying
thank you and running away.
>> Yeah, exactly. But at least the task is
done somehow.
Maybe.
Yeah.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh so yeah, those like again but that
you can't
you have to try it yourself and with
your own workflow even from one day to
another then it's a different workflow.
But all of those orchestration
um
uh all of those orchestration will
matter a lot especially where we are
going to um
pay the real price of a token because
right now we are like uh
the price is subdivided by five
basically.
And uh
Hi Alex.
>> is cheap.
>> Yes, exactly. But uh we don't because we
don't pay the real price. Okay, so
Alex, thank you for your comment on
Twitch. And uh how is it compared to
4.8? That's the uh
chart we just uh passed by.
Um
So 4.8 is in yellow and Sonnet 5 is on
uh in orange and uh this is that's the
price. And like the the price Okay, so
wait.
Uh
Hm.
Wait, maybe Okay, maybe I was reading it
wrong because
it's cheaper, right?
>> Yeah.
>> Cost per task. So it's way cheaper than
4.
uh
>> It It is not comparable with low and low
and medium and medium. You have to run
uh Sonnet high to get Opus low results.
>> You have to run Sonnet Okay, yes, okay.
Yes, it's cheaper. Yes, okay. It's
cheaper. But yeah, again, so the task
while you run again like the the task
that you run the models against matters,
too, because it
based on the token and efficiency run to
execute the task.
So, even that those
by effort level, yes, okay, fair enough.
If the task So, the task need to be the
same.
And then you can compare the tokens.
It's fast as [__] so that's why I like
Yeah, I agree with that. It's It's
definitely
faster than Opus.
Which reasoning are you using, Alex?
Axel, sorry. Axel.
It's looks here.
Okay, yes. And yeah, so that's like
So, did you change like Mitchell, did
you change your
Did you change your workflow
with Sony from 4.8 to Sony 5?
>> [snorts]
>> I did for the lesser
difficult problems because indeed it's
going a lot faster. It feels like you're
actually chatting with a real person
instead of getting all those annoying, I
know better and sorry, I made a mistake.
It goes really smooth.
But, every time I give Opus 4.8 Ultra
code a task and that was what I was
doing up until yesterday,
I could grab two coffee
>> [laughter]
>> before it was done.
>> But, don't you feel that if it's
reasoning higher and it takes more time,
then you the output will be better
because
>> Yeah.
>> took time to think?
>> I hope the output will be better, but
sometimes I just want to see in between
what it's doing. I want to see small
results before I wait like 30 minutes
and create something and I am like,
yeah, I didn't mean it way. Because it
still does some weird things sometimes.
>> Yeah, I know cuz it sometimes is going
like woo, it's just completely like
that's not what I asked, bro.
>> Yes. And then you have spent like a lot
of tokens and 30 minutes of your time.
>> And look at Mitchell like Alex is has
five max 20 x subscription.
>> [laughter]
>> So
>> Alex has like 10 Mac minis all working
all the clock.
>> That's not Alex, that's Axel.
>> Oh, sorry, Axel. Yes.
>> Yeah, I I said I said wrong, too.
But okay, Axel, like what are you
building with like five subscription? Do
you have a team? Do you have a company?
Are you talking maxing in the in the
wind?
>> Yeah.
>> I want to see the output of that.
>> And I hope you're not doing it manually
giving prompts all the time. I hope it
all just loops.
>> I have a startup, yes. Let's go.
Uh Axel Ericsson
defense tech. Ah, makes sense.
That makes sense.
What's the name of the startup? You can
chill You can chill the chat because
there's a lot of people, so
I want Let's Let's see Let's see the
homepage.
Um defense tech, yeah. Well, actually no
[__] you're burning the five
subscription. Oh.
>> Yeah, yeah, and always using ultra
codes, then I guess.
>> industry
industries
industries I'm just going to check it
offline. Ooh, that's cool.
Wow.
Okay.
Uh tech path
chat tabs
noise
van industry
>> It's awesome that you can just build a
company using cloud code.
>> Oh, yeah. I mean I have not one, but
like uh
uh 20
Yeah, but I mean like
>> I don't think Axel is uh building more
company that if it's defense tech that
that's uh
You can be focused on that.
CNN space space contact
uh uh
carrier
Build the things you join the industry.
What what what what? Build the things
you join the industry to build. Build
the things you join the industry to
build. Ah, that's cool.
Uh,
okay. Where is the Okay, good. One
person on Tuesday. Not fair. Okay.
Axel Oh, that's you. Founder Okay. Open
Okay. Okay. Okay. So, what's the state
of the startup right now? Like, uh did
you raise money? Like, what what are you
doing?
>> Well, yeah. And just to say it's not
100% cloud code. We get that, but it
helps a lot.
Yeah.
>> I mean, like, in defense tech
uh if you you have to be you have to
have good skills if you
>> Yeah. Don't just trust anything cloud
tells you. You need to know what you're
doing and check it.
>> I mean, I I hope Axel is know what he's
doing if he's working in that kind of
industry because I can I can push bugs
in production. I can fix them fast,
right? Uh, if it if it's plane off start
shooting stuff that's a that's another
problem.
>> That's a then a bug is a big problem.
Yeah.
>> Nice. I have a lot of previous venture.
Okay, nice.
>> It's really cool to see that people are
using so many cloud code subscriptions
and just
build something insane.
>> Exactly.
Uh, I'm talking with investor right now,
but I'm also funding a lot of myself. I
will
>> Yeah, that's awesome.
>> I've had a lot of uh awesome.
Thanks for joining us, Axel.
How did you find us? Just because of the
title on Twitch? That's cool.
Uh, but yeah, thank you for being in
chat with us.
Okay, and
do you Sony Sony 5 in the planes that
you're building right now? Like
I believe the future in AI, yeah.
It's a whole lot faster, yeah, in the
future in AI. It's a whole
>> Yeah, we are just in the beginning. It's
going to get so much faster, better.
>> Yeah.
>> And
I don't think eventually you need to
think about coding yourself anymore.
Really looking forward to see what we
can do by the end of the year.
>> Yeah. Uh yeah, like that's why like
having those systems
>> in place right now
to work with the models like in 6
months, that's
that's why yeah, it's it's going to be
it's it's more even more important that
what you build right now. But like
yeah, again with like some good
automation and some like routines
automation and some well-defined PRD,
you can build a web startup like pretty
fast.
Uh
chat Cerberus to see the speed of the
future. They build some special ships.
That's cool.
Cerberus AI um
I think I heard about it.
>> Yeah, we will check that after the show.
>> So
right right
>> Maybe that's his other startup.
>> Yeah. [laughter]
No, no no no I mean they got bought by
Wait, no. Wait
back back
Yeah, the first that I think trans like
yeah, they're building
chipsets, yes.
chips
Okay, I forgot what it is, but I already
saw this name on Twitter. I don't know
what they do. Um okay, cool. So, where
we
we went like woo, it's going to be it's
going to be tough.
>> [laughter]
>> We were talking about just about Sony 5.
>> Yeah, check out the chat link to see the
speed of the thing.
Okay.
Um okay, so Sony five and yeah, okay,
fiber five fiber five
like one minute
chance.
Okay,
I'm curious.
Thank.
Oh, wait. I have the W first.
Oh, okay. Meet instantly. Okay, okay.
Give me okay, later later later bro.
Okay, so
we're deploying fiber five back
path path path blog post. Okay, so this
one is like I hate those shenanigans
from Entropic.
But look.
Like thank thank thank.
On Friday, June 12th, the US government
apply export control. Okay, so that's
what happened before. As of today, June
30th, the export control on fiber five
emitters and been has been have been
lifted. So yeah, cool. It's coming back.
Fiber five will be available starting
tomorrow, Wednesday, July 1st to Okay,
so basically today.
Um.
Probably US time. So they're sleeping
right now.
Uh, so okay, so yeah,
clearly for pro max team and select
enterprise fiber five will be included
for up to 50% of the weekly usage limit
through July 7th, after which it will be
available via usage credit.
[__] them.
Well, it is just a full week of of
maximize uh Not maximize. 50% maximize.
Yeah, but still every day you need to
use the full 50%.
Yeah, but No, but no no no, on a weekly.
So you get 50% of your weekly stuff that
will burn your whole subscription. Like,
Axel will buy 10
accounts.
>> Yeah, yeah, but make sure you max what
you can do because afterwards it will be
paid and Fable was good last time.
>> Yeah, I know exactly. But like
for what the cost is, again, I will I
will drop all of my pull requests and
like all of the stuff, but like the
review, I want the execution to be done
with like 5.5
Opus or Sony 5, whatever, and then have
those uh big models to review them
because I think the iteration and like
the
implementation is better when you use
that the cheaper model first and then
the review
uh with the final result and what you
want to push at the end with like a big
gun model.
>> Yeah. Well, that's what I did last time
in a few days that we had Fable. I had
Fable check all my projects and only
write documentation on what was wrong,
what we had to improve, and how to do
it.
And after Fable was banned, I just had
Opus build everything.
>> Yeah. Uh that's cool. Yeah,
I should drop them into the ship ship
game stuff.
Uh that would be fun to see what it go
it goes. Uh
>> Don't burn your tokens on something
you're not going to use.
>> True.
But just for the for the for the little
But yeah.
Um also, GPT-5 is coming up in the next
weeks and has been benchmarked to quite
a bit better than 5.5. That's true. So,
like [snorts] those regulation stuff,
like the US is becoming like the EU.
As well, like
>> For as long as the companies are are in
the US, as soon as you get a better
competitor
outside the US who does release it,
then who who might know what is going to
happen.
>> Well, that's why like models like GLM
5.2 are good for the US to push them
into the like the competi- like the
competitiveness of like I just let those
models
get out because you're going to get
caught up by Chinese open source guys.
>> And eventually, even if China makes a
big model and says the US does not
deliver, we do.
Imagine how many people just use the
Chinese model.
>> Exactly.
Yeah, I know
quite a way. Like even for the videos,
so I've I've generated like some UGC
videos with like those Chinese model
like the students
>> [clears throat]
>> two.
Can't wait for three.
Um
So, I don't like it was basic prompt and
just testing, but
at some point like the voiceover was in
Chinese.
>> [laughter]
>> And
because I didn't specified any text in
English. And but like the the the speed
of like generation and like the quality
of the video, like that was not. So,
yeah, students is a bit different, but
uh
Like you you can imagine an
orchestration between open source
models, open weight model, and close
model. That would be definitely
interesting. Basically, what's Alex
thing was doing at the end of the day.
And from Axel again,
I'm mostly waiting for the Chinese open
weight model to become really good since
that would be
very helpful. Yeah, I I think
that's clear. Like
honestly
there there is there is a world when you
use all of them anyway.
>> Yeah, at least combine them to find the
stuff that the other one is missing.
>> Exactly. And like I mean we we we say
that's
um
like 6 months ago when we um
when we were talking about yeah, like
imagine
open open source model will
give us like ChatGPT 4.5 etc. We still
didn't use any of them.
>> No.
>> And we are the we are we there but uh um
I will also be buying a lot of RTX Park
chips for the local AI usage possibility
when they come out. Yeah, uh do you
follow Alex Finn on X and
YouTube because you're going to like his
content.
Um okay, so
that I don't think there is anything on
on the article that was
talking about now.
Um is Fiber 5 already released to
public? Okay.
>> just going to cost a lot of tokens if
you want to use it after a week.
>> Yes. No, yeah. I'm I'm not using Fiber 5
VIP that's not
>> No.
>> okay, so I'm going to drop Alex Finn
channel
in the chat.
Thank you.
Okay, so yeah, Axel, you can check the
Alex Finn YouTube channel and is Fiber 5
released to public? Not yet. It's coming
in the next few hours.
Just in Europe we are like a Wednesday
first but in the it's US time and it's
coming up today. So
just wait.
And uh buy a new sub a new sub.
>> Yeah.
>> Or wait for 5.6 or 2.4.
>> have enough.
>> Uh
No, uh okay, so I'm French but I live in
Malta because
French friends are
crazy country. I can win that. Win that.
Win that.
We're going to win the World Cup but
other than that can't work in there.
Um okay, so reaction from the timeline.
Thanks. Thanks.
Okay, so see you
talking about a little bit of Alex Finn.
But, uh big Okay, so
uh
that Febel 5 will be included 50% of the
weekly. So, yeah, we already see talk
about that.
Um we were actually going to get 100%
usage from June 9th to June 23rd. Uh 15
days. Instead, we get 100% usage for 3
days and 50% usage for seven.
>> Yeah. And then still it has to be
released because I don't have access
yet.
>> Yeah, true.
>> If you're in the last batch of getting
access, then you you lose a lot of days.
>> No, it's it's going to be nuts. Um
Tropic plans to bring back Febel 5
tomorrow. They're making us wait. Okay,
so yes, that was the later that uh
where we got the news first.
Um so, that's it, I think. Uh film about
Open AI. Yeah, okay.
That That the comparison between Febel 5
and 5.6 will be definitely interesting.
>> Mhm.
>> Um
>> And then it's good to see it from other
people and not just their own
benchmarks.
>> Yeah.
Uh you're you're sweating, bro. Okay, so
sorry about that, but uh we're go we're
going to bring the the cup at home.
>> [laughter]
>> Uh okay. Puff puff puff. Okay, yes. Uh
artificial analysis uh Claude Sony uh
I I
What? Achieves the 53 of the artificial
analysis intelligence index, but with a
promotional pricing will cost more per
task than 4.8.
Um
number of fifth models on the artificial
analysis intelligence index, which is
not because it's a Sony model.
It's crazy.
>> Yeah. And then still imagine what we had
had like 6 months ago.
>> Yeah, exactly. No, it's it's it's
insane.
Uh Max effort Sony works harder than
previous Anthropic model. It used 40%
more output token per intelligence in
this
Okay. And three x the agentic stones for
knowledge work evaluation.
Yeah, okay. That's That's See, that's
the actual That's why it's not that
cheap.
>> No.
>> Yeah. I mean, maybe it's because of the
lunch.
Uh,
could fine-tune those
They could fine-tune post-training on
the Anthropic side, but yeah.
Um, yeah. Like
I mean, if we get more intelligence, I
don't know. Like the workflows from 4.8
and Fable 5 that they're using in
neutral code mode will be interesting
for that because I Yeah, I'm going to
build my subscription like crazy again.
Yeah. I don't know, man.
Uh, Claude 2.5 cost more per task than
4.8 before accounting for push
promotional pricing.
Uh, 2.5 cost 2.29 per task on the
intelligence index a two x increase
compared to 4.8
4.6.
Yeah.
Yeah. I mean
>> That's a big difference if you compare
it to the chart, right? Even gives you a
discount at this moment.
>> And 50% more than Claude Opus.
4.8.
Yeah, okay. It's cheaper than Fable 5
basically.
Look sick.
Uh, this is driven entirely by increased
token usage. Yes. Okay, so yes, like the
price per token is cheap cheap or like
same price, but it used more tokens.
That's sad.
Uh, matches our performance uh, 4.8 on
agentic codex
knowledge work work task. Yeah, because
I think the jump will be on five, right?
Uh Sony is still sitting behind in
largest its larger siblings. Yeah,
that's normal.
Uh okay, wait.
Sony five scores 50 70% and this is a
four 14 point higher than its
predecessor, but behind GLM 5.2. Hmm.
Claude Opus and Fable and GPT five 5.5
XI and Pro.
Pro is only on API, right?
Mhm. Yeah. [clears throat]
Um Sony five also shows significant
improvement
over Sony 4.6. Yeah, no [__]
Uh cool cool cool. Informative. Okay.
So, Fable five
4.8 max
5.5 XI. Yeah, okay, that's not bad.
>> Yeah, it's just waiting for 5.6.
>> Yeah.
>> From OpenAI.
>> Yeah, because like now we are like one
generation behind them. So,
Yeah, it's going to be it's going to be
interesting. Like the release will be
not
>> Where is Mistral?
It's a mystery.
>> Oh my god. Really?
>> But you see the old models with which
you were happy a few months ago are now
all the way back. Nobody is even looking
at them
unless you bought like a subscription
for four year.
>> Yeah,
but also like the bench like the max the
ceiling of those benchmark with was
were lower, too, right? Now we expect
like
Yeah, we expect like Sony
Sony five to be at least the level of
like all of those big ass models.
>> Yes.
>> Like if you don't get 53 on the
index intelligence uh
intelligence index, my bad.
Um then I'm not going to you.
Next Mistral
uh next Mistral models is rumored to be
released by July 15th.
Okay, yeah, let's go.
Two weeks later.
Can't wait. Can't wait to not use it.
>> [snorts]
>> Okay, close to me. Okay, so that's
better ask.
It's better mixed
benchmark for Sony 5, no?
Not going to that charging more than
Opus for 6.5. That's kind of rough.
I mean, yeah.
If Opus is already doing the job for
most people, yeah, that's true. Do you
have like limitation of 4.8 right now?
>> No, I have no limitations.
But eventually, yeah, all the people
reacting are just devs who
they
take the effort to research it fully and
compare it. Most of the people are just
reading, "Hey, it is more cheaper, it's
better, and it is discounted, so
everybody will just enable it."
>> My bad.
>> Bless you.
>> Okay, and GPT 5.6 rumored to be July
11th. Uh
Are you also like, "Trust me, bro?"
>> Yeah.
Well,
it [clears throat] was said that it
should already have been Yeah, they are
delaying, right?
Otherwise, they have to block it as
well.
>> Yeah, like it was in preview, and then
they were waiting for the government to
validate it because they didn't want to
get banned. But, what's your take on
that? Like
on those bans by the government because
the models are getting distilled/stolen,
and then Amazon complained that
Fable can't find
Ax.
>> You know what? Eventually, they also
said that they were the government and
other stuff was getting hacked by
Flipper and they couldn't prevent it.
So,
they were afraid of what it was going to
do. And I get it. If people jailbreak it
and then just use it to hack everything,
you don't want to have it out, but
everything will eventually just do that.
>> Yeah, but okay. So, also it's like you
know a pen test like it's it's easier to
find hacks when you have access to the
code base than if you do
if you try to enter an infrastructure
from the outside without any knowledge
whatsoever and it's a black box, right?
>> Yeah, yeah. So, the difference between
black, gray, and white.
>> Uh
No, that's
like a black hat is like a bad guy and a
gray hat is mixed.
>> Oh, no. I also mean they also name it
for about how much do you know about the
environment and how many
>> Yeah, okay. My bad. Yes, okay. Black
box, gray box, white box. Yeah, okay.
Okay. Okay. My bad. My bad. I
misunderstood. But,
okay. So, yes. So, if you know nothing
So, and Amazon with his
uh its red team
basically
connected the what they wanted to test
to Flipper Zero 5 and say, "Oh, yeah.
Flipper Zero 5 found some issues and we
are capable blah blah blah." But, yeah.
No [__] It's because you give it your
infrastructure.
>> Yeah. But, Flipper also found Linux
issues that have been there for over 10
years and nobody abused them because
people didn't know.
>> Yeah, no. Exactly.
And I don't like also it could be like
the cost of exploiting those issues
is too high even for an AI / a previous
black hat hacker to
to do it.
I don't I don't know.
Uh at 2 we stream block list. Bam. I'm
not buying viewer, bro. Bye-bye.
Uh okay. So, another
reaction from Bridge Mind. You know, the
guy is streaming like
uh vibe coding
uh until you reach 1 million
in revenue.
>> I haven't seen him. I'm not one of his
viewers.
>> Okay. Me neither, but I see him on the
timeline. He is quite He's quite good at
distribution, so that's interesting. Uh
and his a point of view about yeah,
Fable and
uh Sony.
Uh
Anthropic mentions everyone with the
original post language. Yeah. Like Oh,
yeah. Also,
uh in the near term, some routine task
like coding and debugging will fall back
to Opus 4.8.
>> That's like what every bus everybody
does with it right now.
>> What are you doing except coding with
[__] Opus?
>> Well, I think they want to make it like
a a cyber product.
>> Yeah. Yeah, but that's still coding.
Like a cyber or not?
>> Oh, no. I mean,
defense and and hacks and security
issues and
>> I mean,
that's where the big money is, right?
That's why Axel is building a startup in
tech defense, too, right?
>> Yes.
>> But yeah, it's
It feels
closed written and not human reviewed.
>> No. They are just putting in some words
so they can always fall back to a
different model if needed.
>> Yeah, but then I Bro, at this level,
like you need a lawyer
to review what you generated for the on
the article.
Um okay. So, Fable 5 is back. Blah blah
blah. Fable enough with its return. As
every benchmark finds original 12 Fable
5, the moment assets is the more We are
re-running everything. Fair enough. Fair
enough. Uh cool cool cool. And then I
wanted his
uh
feedback about Sony. Yes. So,
we back.
Token efficiency is so bad it's end up
being more expensive than Claude 4.8
Opus 4.8.
Uh
that kind of sad.
That's the article we are
we just read.
Um
Yeah.
If and that's why
Theo was also talking about when say
like
OpenAI is focusing on token efficiency
because it's also compute, right? If
Anthropic is [__] up with those token
consumption, no [__] they don't have
enough compute.
Yeah, well. But if they fix that, if
they are efficient and they have the
smartest model for coding etc.,
that's a banger.
>> The thing is we don't know, right? We
don't know if they need to optimize it
and it will be better later. We don't
know if they just wanted to push and
couldn't push fast enough, so they agree
with using more tokens and they can
reach the level that they want.
So, if you want to boost like a few
points on on on the comparison on the
benchmark, you can also just let it burn
more tokens and it will be better.
>> Yeah.
Yeah, and like the more token you use,
the more subscription you burn, so let's
go.
>> Yeah.
>> And see, that's Bridge Mind, that's what
he's doing every day all day.
>> Well,
why not? If he gets to 1 million, let's
see how he does.
>> [snorts]
>> Uh okay, Sonnet 5 taking request, blah
blah blah, cool cool cool. Okay, that's
it. So, that was
>> So, for me the question is to you, what
are you going to do? Keep using Opus 4.8
or are you using Sonnet 5 by default? Or
just say I use 4.8 Ultra Code and have
them both.
>> So, yeah, I think for now I'm going to
keep my
workflow that I have now because
uh so
the P&E is playing uh but by Opus and
then it's sent to GitHub. Then I I have
those routines that run on the Codex app
uh that picked up those task, implement
them
um and then I have those reviews with uh
4.8 Ultra code and then I push
everything to master and I publish. Uh I
don't think like Sony 5 um
um
would change anything with that because
it still works. It's just like the split
is kind of like a cool. Actually yeah,
maybe I can optimize it or have
different routines um
and more actions where the cheapest
model and if Sony 5 is smarter than 4.6
then I I will have a
better cleaner
GitHub board.
Yeah.
So, that's what I like.
I like I like to have clean board.
>> Yes. Have it empty and everything built.
>> Yeah. And auto
we we saw me reviewing anything.
>> [laughter]
>> Yeah.
>> I just in the app on production and say
oh yeah, it's broken. Claude, fix it.
>> Yes.
When he's offline, make sure it works
when he comes back.
>> Exactly.
>> Oh I I know did you ever use like the
Claude extension like to test the app in
the browser?
>> No.
Do it. It's good. It's very good.
>> Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like uh
>> I've been testing so many stuff and they
bring out so many features and most of
the time I just fall back to Claude code
and have him do everything.
>> Yeah. No, no, no, but that then Claude
code has a Claude extension in your
browser that you download and it connect
to your Claude session and then it open
the browser and it can click, click,
click. So, it can test your button, test
everything, and you're going to love it.
>> Okay, that's cool.
>> It's not something that I vibe coded or
something. It's
It's an official extension. So, let's
go.
>> It's got actually built it himself.
>> Exactly.
>> Yes, that's great.
>> I saw a tweet about
I don't know. Yeah, how much is real,
but yeah, whatever. I do for Claude
Sonnet 5 can build
Chrome extension to add friends on
LinkedIn. And it send a message
automatically. And using this kind of
the same Chrome extension than Claude
before, [clears throat]
but you can have those
This is the extension connected to your
LinkedIn account to create more friends,
like
connect more friends on LinkedIn. And uh
Yeah. So, there is that, too.
But okay, should we wrap it up? I think
we're good.
>> Yes, okay, cool.
Yeah, okay. So, I mean, I kind of
conclude already anyway.
But yeah, what about what about you?
Like how Sonnet 5 will be
um entering your workflows, or are you
going to um
to wait for February 5 to burn
your subscription?
>> No, yeah, I'm sure for going to wait for
February 5 cuz
it's going to review everything I've
built in the past few days.
>> Mhm.
>> But all my API setup for for that's
connecting to my software,
I'm going to upgrade to Sonnet 5. Just
see what it does and see if I see a peak
or a change in my cost. And if it is
around the same amount, I don't mind.
I'm just keeping
Sonnet 5.
>> Yeah, okay. That makes sense.
That makes sense. Okay, cool.
Uh Axel, test Cerebrus.
We will do that
definitely. And if it's cool, like if
you gave us something cool to test,
maybe we can do even like talk about it
in a video / live stream anyway.
Uh Uh but Axel, thank you so much for
joining the chat and
uh Lucas too, thank you.
And Michelle, thank you for your time.
And see you next week. Yes, next week
about open models if 5.6 doesn't drop in
then.
Um and yeah, subscribe for uh blah blah
Subscribe, comments, like, share the
video because we need more views.
>> Do everything.
>> Thank you.
>> Bye.
>> I